{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213883063","data":{"timestamp":" 947213883063"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213884833","data":{"timestamp":" 947213884833"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213889914","data":{"timestamp":" 947213889914"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213891279","data":{"timestamp":" 947213891279"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213892409","data":{"timestamp":" 947213892409"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213893394","data":{"timestamp":" 947213893394"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KIANGAZI"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213895072","data":{"timestamp":" 947213895072"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIANGAZI"," userResponse":" KIANGAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213895450","data":{"timestamp":" 947213895449"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213896741","data":{"timestamp":" 947213896741"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213903730","data":{"timestamp":" 947213903730"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213906251","data":{"timestamp":" 947213906251"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUNA"," userResponse":" HAKUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213915183","data":{"timestamp":" 947213915183"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213923319","data":{"timestamp":" 947213923319"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213925262","data":{"timestamp":" 947213925262"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213926865","data":{"timestamp":" 947213926865"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213927791","data":{"timestamp":" 947213927791"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213928858","data":{"timestamp":" 947213928858"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213934788","data":{"timestamp":" 947213934788"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ISIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213938823","data":{"timestamp":" 947213938822"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ISIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" ISIPOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213941810","data":{"timestamp":" 947213941810"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213947172","data":{"timestamp":" 947213947171"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213950426","data":{"timestamp":" 947213950426"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213953603","data":{"timestamp":" 947213953603"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213959262","data":{"timestamp":" 947213959261"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213961152","data":{"timestamp":" 947213961152"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213961452","data":{"timestamp":" 947213961452"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKWENDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213965381","data":{"timestamp":" 947213965380"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKWENDA"," userResponse":" START_WALIKWENDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213967243","data":{"timestamp":" 947213967243"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKWENDA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213969020","data":{"timestamp":" 947213969020"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" MBALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213969102","data":{"timestamp":" 947213969102"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" START_KWENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213971132","data":{"timestamp":" 947213971132"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213972066","data":{"timestamp":" 947213972066"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" START_KWENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213973052","data":{"timestamp":" 947213973052"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" MBALI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213974687","data":{"timestamp":" 947213974686"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213980227","data":{"timestamp":" 947213980227"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ULIOKUWA"," userResponse":" START_ULIOKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213981911","data":{"timestamp":" 947213981910"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ULIOKUWA"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213983805","data":{"timestamp":" 947213983805"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIOKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213985962","data":{"timestamp":" 947213985961"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213987271","data":{"timestamp":" 947213987271"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213989865","data":{"timestamp":" 947213989865"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MATAMU"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213993216","data":{"timestamp":" 947213993216"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATAMU"," userResponse":" MATAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213997131","data":{"timestamp":" 947213997131"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213997452","data":{"timestamp":" 947213997452"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MKUYU"," userResponse":" START_MKUYU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214002837","data":{"timestamp":" 947214002837"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUYU"," userResponse":" MKUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214004124","data":{"timestamp":" 947214004124"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ULIOKUWA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214011991","data":{"timestamp":" 947214011991"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ULIOKUWA"," userResponse":" MKUYU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214013883","data":{"timestamp":" 947214013882"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIOKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214014666","data":{"timestamp":" 947214014666"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214029124","data":{"timestamp":" 947214029124"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" START_MBALI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214030742","data":{"timestamp":" 947214030742"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214033218","data":{"timestamp":" 947214033218"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" START_KWENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214034439","data":{"timestamp":" 947214034439"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214035088","data":{"timestamp":" 947214035088"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTO"," userResponse":" MTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214038039","data":{"timestamp":" 947214038039"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214040632","data":{"timestamp":" 947214040632"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" START_KUWALETEA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214042158","data":{"timestamp":" 947214042158"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214044516","data":{"timestamp":" 947214044516"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIRUDI"," userResponse":" WALIRUDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214044520","data":{"timestamp":" 947214044520"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214052784","data":{"timestamp":" 947214052784"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAMEBEBA"," userResponse":" MTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214056738","data":{"timestamp":" 947214056737"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAMEBEBA"," userResponse":" START_WAMEBEBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214058390","data":{"timestamp":" 947214058390"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMEBEBA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214063084","data":{"timestamp":" 947214063084"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" START_WAMEBEBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214065190","data":{"timestamp":" 947214065190"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" START_MATUNDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214066918","data":{"timestamp":" 947214066917"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214072299","data":{"timestamp":" 947214072299"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214074226","data":{"timestamp":" 947214074226"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214074230","data":{"timestamp":" 947214074229"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUYU"," userResponse":" MKUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214077546","data":{"timestamp":" 947214077546"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUWALETEA"," userResponse":" START_KWENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214079073","data":{"timestamp":" 947214079073"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUWALETEA"," userResponse":" START_KUWALETEA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214080765","data":{"timestamp":" 947214080764"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWALETEA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214081538","data":{"timestamp":" 947214081537"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NDUGU"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214082725","data":{"timestamp":" 947214082725"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDUGU"," userResponse":" NDUGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214083943","data":{"timestamp":" 947214083943"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ZAO"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214085951","data":{"timestamp":" 947214085951"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ZAO"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214087572","data":{"timestamp":" 947214087571"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAO"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214090349","data":{"timestamp":" 947214090349"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOYAONA"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214094269","data":{"timestamp":" 947214094268"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOYAONA"," userResponse":" START_ALIPOYAONA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214096403","data":{"timestamp":" 947214096403"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOYAONA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214097490","data":{"timestamp":" 947214097490"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214106161","data":{"timestamp":" 947214106161"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HAYO"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214107924","data":{"timestamp":" 947214107924"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HAYO"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214109493","data":{"timestamp":" 947214109493"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYO"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214111686","data":{"timestamp":" 947214111686"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" BUIBUI"," userResponse":" KIANGAZI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214114790","data":{"timestamp":" 947214114790"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" BUIBUI"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214116464","data":{"timestamp":" 947214116464"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUIBUI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214118469","data":{"timestamp":" 947214118469"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" MBALI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214120871","data":{"timestamp":" 947214120871"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" KULIKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214122550","data":{"timestamp":" 947214122550"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214124409","data":{"timestamp":" 947214124409"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIDONDOKWA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214126212","data":{"timestamp":" 947214126212"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIDONDOKWA"," userResponse":" MATE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214128224","data":{"timestamp":" 947214128224"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIDONDOKWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214129701","data":{"timestamp":" 947214129701"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" MATAMU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214131506","data":{"timestamp":" 947214131506"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" ISIPOKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214132901","data":{"timestamp":" 947214132900"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214133071","data":{"timestamp":" 947214133070"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MATE"," userResponse":" START_KUNGURU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214134466","data":{"timestamp":" 947214134466"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MATE"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214135966","data":{"timestamp":" 947214135966"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214142592","data":{"timestamp":" 947214142592"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214143465","data":{"timestamp":" 947214143465"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214158756","data":{"timestamp":" 947214158755"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEWEZAJE"," userResponse":" MTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214159873","data":{"timestamp":" 947214159872"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEWEZAJE"," userResponse":" START_ANGEWEZAJE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214161808","data":{"timestamp":" 947214161808"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEWEZAJE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214164111","data":{"timestamp":" 947214164111"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUYAPATA"," userResponse":" START_KWENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214165873","data":{"timestamp":" 947214165873"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUYAPATA"," userResponse":" ALIDONDOKWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214167732","data":{"timestamp":" 947214167732"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUYAPATA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214168884","data":{"timestamp":" 947214168884"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214170194","data":{"timestamp":" 947214170194"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" ZAO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214171896","data":{"timestamp":" 947214171896"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214174766","data":{"timestamp":" 947214174766"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYO"," userResponse":" HAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214193975","data":{"timestamp":" 947214193974"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214193990","data":{"timestamp":" 947214193990"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNDA"," userResponse":" TUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214194004","data":{"timestamp":" 947214194003"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214195675","data":{"timestamp":" 947214195675"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HALIKUTOSHA"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214198239","data":{"timestamp":" 947214198238"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HALIKUTOSHA"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214200168","data":{"timestamp":" 947214200168"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HALIKUTOSHA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214204360","data":{"timestamp":" 947214204360"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIRUDI"," userResponse":" START_HALIKUTOSHA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214207877","data":{"timestamp":" 947214207876"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIRUDI"," userResponse":" ALIRUDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214210209","data":{"timestamp":" 947214210209"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214210577","data":{"timestamp":" 947214210576"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214210856","data":{"timestamp":" 947214210856"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214211687","data":{"timestamp":" 947214211687"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PILI"," userResponse":" PILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214215446","data":{"timestamp":" 947214215445"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAFANYA"," userResponse":" AKAFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214217763","data":{"timestamp":" 947214217763"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214220798","data":{"timestamp":" 947214220798"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" AKAFANYA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214222247","data":{"timestamp":" 947214222247"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214223389","data":{"timestamp":" 947214223389"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214225095","data":{"timestamp":" 947214225095"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214229795","data":{"timestamp":" 947214229795"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AMEFANYA"," userResponse":" AKAFANYA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214231047","data":{"timestamp":" 947214231047"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AMEFANYA"," userResponse":" TUNDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214232917","data":{"timestamp":" 947214232917"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEFANYA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214238618","data":{"timestamp":" 947214238618"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214240662","data":{"timestamp":" 947214240661"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" AMEFANYA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214242136","data":{"timestamp":" 947214242135"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alirudi kwa mara ya pili akafanya vile alikuwa amefanya tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214262255","data":{"timestamp":" 947214262255"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPORUDI"," userResponse":" START_ALIPORUDI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214265066","data":{"timestamp":" 947214265066"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPORUDI"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214267070","data":{"timestamp":" 947214267070"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPORUDI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214268348","data":{"timestamp":" 947214268348"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214271481","data":{"timestamp":" 947214271480"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214272904","data":{"timestamp":" 947214272904"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214274937","data":{"timestamp":" 947214274937"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214274940","data":{"timestamp":" 947214274940"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214280649","data":{"timestamp":" 947214280649"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214281714","data":{"timestamp":" 947214281714"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214283306","data":{"timestamp":" 947214283304"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214285594","data":{"timestamp":" 947214285594"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIANZA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214289014","data":{"timestamp":" 947214289013"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WALIANZA"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214290597","data":{"timestamp":" 947214290597"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIANZA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214294493","data":{"timestamp":" 947214294493"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUMSHUKU"," userResponse":" START_ALIPORUDI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214297066","data":{"timestamp":" 947214297066"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUMSHUKU"," userResponse":" TUNDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214298770","data":{"timestamp":" 947214298769"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliporudi mara ya tatu kunguru walianza kumshuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMSHUKU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214300301","data":{"timestamp":" 947214300301"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214301105","data":{"timestamp":" 947214301104"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214303339","data":{"timestamp":" 947214303339"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214305040","data":{"timestamp":" 947214305040"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214306506","data":{"timestamp":" 947214306506"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214309258","data":{"timestamp":" 947214309258"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" UNARUDI"," userResponse":" KUOMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214314426","data":{"timestamp":" 947214314426"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" UNARUDI"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214316149","data":{"timestamp":" 947214316148"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNARUDI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214317302","data":{"timestamp":" 947214317302"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HAPA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214319000","data":{"timestamp":" 947214319000"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPA"," userResponse":" HAPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214319004","data":{"timestamp":" 947214319004"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214321871","data":{"timestamp":" 947214321869"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214323771","data":{"timestamp":" 947214323770"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214324656","data":{"timestamp":" 947214324656"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214326448","data":{"timestamp":" 947214326448"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUOMBA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214327721","data":{"timestamp":" 947214327720"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUOMBA"," userResponse":" HAPA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214329334","data":{"timestamp":" 947214329334"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUOMBA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214332425","data":{"timestamp":" 947214332425"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KAA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214334709","data":{"timestamp":" 947214334709"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KAA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214336036","data":{"timestamp":" 947214336036"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214337188","data":{"timestamp":" 947214337188"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214340529","data":{"timestamp":" 947214340529"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214344418","data":{"timestamp":" 947214344417"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini unarudi hapa mara kwa mara kuomba kaa la moto?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214346338","data":{"timestamp":" 947214346338"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" START_HAPA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214347390","data":{"timestamp":" 947214347390"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214349021","data":{"timestamp":" 947214349021"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214351498","data":{"timestamp":" 947214351498"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKAJIBU"," userResponse":" START_AMEFANYA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214354044","data":{"timestamp":" 947214354044"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAJIBU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214361525","data":{"timestamp":" 947214361525"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KUMSHUKU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214372218","data":{"timestamp":" 947214372218"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214381681","data":{"timestamp":" 947214381681"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214404735","data":{"timestamp":" 947214404735"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIKIFIKA"," userResponse":" NIKIFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214404739","data":{"timestamp":" 947214404739"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214411356","data":{"timestamp":" 947214411356"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAA"," userResponse":" KAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214412447","data":{"timestamp":" 947214412447"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HUWA"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214415770","data":{"timestamp":" 947214415770"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUWA"," userResponse":" HUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214418503","data":{"timestamp":" 947214418503"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LIMEZIMIKA"," userResponse":" KAA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214428181","data":{"timestamp":" 947214428180"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" LIMEZIMIKA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214430168","data":{"timestamp":" 947214430168"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajibu kila wakati nikifika nyumbani kaa huwa limezimika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIMEZIMIKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214434469","data":{"timestamp":" 947214434469"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214436974","data":{"timestamp":" 947214436974"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIMWAMBIA"," userResponse":" KUOMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214440902","data":{"timestamp":" 947214440902"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WALIMWAMBIA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214442911","data":{"timestamp":" 947214442911"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIMWAMBIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214446017","data":{"timestamp":" 947214446017"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214450893","data":{"timestamp":" 947214450893"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TAMAA"," userResponse":" START_AMEFANYA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214465415","data":{"timestamp":" 947214465414"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" TAMAA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214466957","data":{"timestamp":" 947214466957"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMAA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214478865","data":{"timestamp":" 947214478865"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" KUOMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214489697","data":{"timestamp":" 947214489697"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214492994","data":{"timestamp":" 947214492994"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214519871","data":{"timestamp":" 947214519871"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" HAPA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214521595","data":{"timestamp":" 947214521594"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214523448","data":{"timestamp":" 947214523448"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CHETU"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214530407","data":{"timestamp":" 947214530407"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" CHETU"," userResponse":" START_WALIMWAMBIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214531657","data":{"timestamp":" 947214531656"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Una tamaa ya chakula chetu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHETU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214537563","data":{"timestamp":" 947214537563"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Si kweli Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SI"," userResponse":" START_MOTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214552659","data":{"timestamp":" 947214552659"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Si kweli Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" SI"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214554037","data":{"timestamp":" 947214554037"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Si kweli Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214559585","data":{"timestamp":" 947214559585"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Si kweli Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWELI"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214564201","data":{"timestamp":" 947214564201"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Si kweli Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KWELI"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214565698","data":{"timestamp":" 947214565698"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Si kweli Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWELI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214566660","data":{"timestamp":" 947214566660"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Si kweli Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" HUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214569090","data":{"timestamp":" 947214569090"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Si kweli Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" HAPA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214570731","data":{"timestamp":" 947214570730"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Si kweli Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214571503","data":{"timestamp":" 947214571503"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Si kweli Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214573046","data":{"timestamp":" 947214573046"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Si kweli Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214574854","data":{"timestamp":" 947214574854"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Si kweli Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214591545","data":{"timestamp":" 947214591545"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru wakamwonea huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HALAFU"," userResponse":" HALAFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214594896","data":{"timestamp":" 947214594896"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru wakamwonea huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKAANZA"," userResponse":" KWELI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214598835","data":{"timestamp":" 947214598835"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru wakamwonea huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AKAANZA"," userResponse":" KWELI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214600629","data":{"timestamp":" 947214600629"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru wakamwonea huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAANZA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214605539","data":{"timestamp":" 947214605539"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru wakamwonea huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KULIA"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214607408","data":{"timestamp":" 947214607407"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru wakamwonea huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KULIA"," userResponse":" START_KULIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214608896","data":{"timestamp":" 947214608896"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru wakamwonea huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214611984","data":{"timestamp":" 947214611984"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru wakamwonea huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214614676","data":{"timestamp":" 947214614676"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru wakamwonea huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAMWONEA"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214616061","data":{"timestamp":" 947214616061"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru wakamwonea huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAMWONEA"," userResponse":" KUMSHUKU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214617946","data":{"timestamp":" 947214617945"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru wakamwonea huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAMWONEA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214619422","data":{"timestamp":" 947214619422"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru wakamwonea huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HURUMA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214621194","data":{"timestamp":" 947214621194"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru wakamwonea huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HURUMA"," userResponse":" HURUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214622973","data":{"timestamp":" 947214622973"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru wakamwonea huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214624860","data":{"timestamp":" 947214624859"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru wakamwonea huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214626199","data":{"timestamp":" 947214626199"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru wakamwonea huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214628229","data":{"timestamp":" 947214628229"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SAWASAWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214630109","data":{"timestamp":" 947214630109"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" SAWASAWA"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214632073","data":{"timestamp":" 947214632072"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAWASAWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214635553","data":{"timestamp":" 947214635553"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214637670","data":{"timestamp":" 947214637670"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" START_KUNGURU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214639243","data":{"timestamp":" 947214639242"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214643707","data":{"timestamp":" 947214643707"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAKASEMA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214645336","data":{"timestamp":" 947214645336"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAKASEMA"," userResponse":" PILI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214647163","data":{"timestamp":" 947214647162"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKASEMA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214649304","data":{"timestamp":" 947214649304"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" BEBA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214651452","data":{"timestamp":" 947214651452"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BEBA"," userResponse":" BEBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214651456","data":{"timestamp":" 947214651455"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAA"," userResponse":" KAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214652542","data":{"timestamp":" 947214652541"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINGINE"," userResponse":" JINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214652625","data":{"timestamp":" 947214652625"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" NAWE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214654273","data":{"timestamp":" 947214654273"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214654276","data":{"timestamp":" 947214654276"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214659370","data":{"timestamp":" 947214659369"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214664950","data":{"timestamp":" 947214664950"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KESHO"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214667653","data":{"timestamp":" 947214667653"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KESHO"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214669107","data":{"timestamp":" 947214669107"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KESHO"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214670985","data":{"timestamp":" 947214670985"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MAPEMA"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214672479","data":{"timestamp":" 947214672478"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MAPEMA"," userResponse":" SI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214673970","data":{"timestamp":" 947214673969"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAPEMA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214675143","data":{"timestamp":" 947214675143"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" KWELI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214677181","data":{"timestamp":" 947214677181"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" KUOMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214679031","data":{"timestamp":" 947214679031"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214681224","data":{"timestamp":" 947214681224"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUTAENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214685376","data":{"timestamp":" 947214685376"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NAWE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214690235","data":{"timestamp":" 947214690234"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NAWE"," userResponse":" TAMAA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214691687","data":{"timestamp":" 947214691687"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAWE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214692378","data":{"timestamp":" 947214692378"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214692461","data":{"timestamp":" 947214692461"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MKUYU"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214697580","data":{"timestamp":" 947214697580"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUYU"," userResponse":" MKUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214698627","data":{"timestamp":" 947214698627"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WENYE"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214700305","data":{"timestamp":" 947214700305"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENYE"," userResponse":" WENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214700461","data":{"timestamp":" 947214700461"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  Beba kaa jingine la moto na kesho mapema asubuhi tutaenda nawe kwenye mkuyu wenye matunda."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214706457","data":{"timestamp":" 947214706457"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" MANYOYA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214710984","data":{"timestamp":" 947214710984"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" MBAWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214712840","data":{"timestamp":" 947214712840"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214715217","data":{"timestamp":" 947214715217"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOFUATA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214733091","data":{"timestamp":" 947214733091"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" START_ALIMCHANGIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214740124","data":{"timestamp":" 947214740124"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214744403","data":{"timestamp":" 947214744402"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214746925","data":{"timestamp":" 947214746925"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMCHANGIA"," userResponse":" START_ALIMCHANGIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214758885","data":{"timestamp":" 947214758885"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMCHANGIA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214760910","data":{"timestamp":" 947214760909"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMCHANGIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214763192","data":{"timestamp":" 947214763192"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214776009","data":{"timestamp":" 947214776009"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214776021","data":{"timestamp":" 947214776021"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYOYA"," userResponse":" MANYOYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214782432","data":{"timestamp":" 947214782432"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKAPATA"," userResponse":" START_AKAPATA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214791338","data":{"timestamp":" 947214791338"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAPATA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214800721","data":{"timestamp":" 947214800720"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MBAWA"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214810885","data":{"timestamp":" 947214810884"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAWA"," userResponse":" MBAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214813431","data":{"timestamp":" 947214813431"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" MBAWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214822085","data":{"timestamp":" 947214822085"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" MKUYU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214823704","data":{"timestamp":" 947214823703"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214826583","data":{"timestamp":" 947214826583"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKARUKA"," userResponse":" MKUYU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214831187","data":{"timestamp":" 947214831187"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKARUKA"," userResponse":" AKARUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214832016","data":{"timestamp":" 947214832015"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214833483","data":{"timestamp":" 947214833483"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214833888","data":{"timestamp":" 947214833888"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214834880","data":{"timestamp":" 947214834880"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MKUYU"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214841141","data":{"timestamp":" 947214841141"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUYU"," userResponse":" MKUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214841144","data":{"timestamp":" 947214841144"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIOKUWA"," userResponse":" ULIOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214843733","data":{"timestamp":" 947214843733"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" KATIKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214843736","data":{"timestamp":" 947214843736"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214843739","data":{"timestamp":" 947214843739"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi akaruka hadi kwenye mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTO"," userResponse":" MTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214846880","data":{"timestamp":" 947214846879"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoona matunda yale matamu aliyataka yote peke yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOONA"," userResponse":" MTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214848742","data":{"timestamp":" 947214848742"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoona matunda yale matamu aliyataka yote peke yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOONA"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214850604","data":{"timestamp":" 947214850603"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoona matunda yale matamu aliyataka yote peke yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOONA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214853303","data":{"timestamp":" 947214853302"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoona matunda yale matamu aliyataka yote peke yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214856663","data":{"timestamp":" 947214856663"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoona matunda yale matamu aliyataka yote peke yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214865537","data":{"timestamp":" 947214865537"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoona matunda yale matamu aliyataka yote peke yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALE"," userResponse":" YALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214865767","data":{"timestamp":" 947214865766"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoona matunda yale matamu aliyataka yote peke yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATAMU"," userResponse":" MATAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214871290","data":{"timestamp":" 947214871290"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoona matunda yale matamu aliyataka yote peke yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYATAKA"," userResponse":" START_ALIYATAKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214872476","data":{"timestamp":" 947214872476"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoona matunda yale matamu aliyataka yote peke yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYATAKA"," userResponse":" YOTE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214874516","data":{"timestamp":" 947214874515"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoona matunda yale matamu aliyataka yote peke yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYATAKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214877683","data":{"timestamp":" 947214877683"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoona matunda yale matamu aliyataka yote peke yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214878462","data":{"timestamp":" 947214878461"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoona matunda yale matamu aliyataka yote peke yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" YOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214880084","data":{"timestamp":" 947214880084"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoona matunda yale matamu aliyataka yote peke yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" PEKE"," userResponse":" MKUYU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214882619","data":{"timestamp":" 947214882619"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoona matunda yale matamu aliyataka yote peke yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" PEKE"," userResponse":" KATIKATI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214883991","data":{"timestamp":" 947214883990"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoona matunda yale matamu aliyataka yote peke yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEKE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214885151","data":{"timestamp":" 947214885151"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoona matunda yale matamu aliyataka yote peke yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214888988","data":{"timestamp":" 947214888988"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoona matunda yale matamu aliyataka yote peke yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214890418","data":{"timestamp":" 947214890417"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoona matunda yale matamu aliyataka yote peke yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214892760","data":{"timestamp":" 947214892760"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214896007","data":{"timestamp":" 947214896007"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214897250","data":{"timestamp":" 947214897249"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214898168","data":{"timestamp":" 947214898168"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" MTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214900223","data":{"timestamp":" 947214900223"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214901938","data":{"timestamp":" 947214901937"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" MANYOYA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214905868","data":{"timestamp":" 947214905868"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" ASUBUHI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214907435","data":{"timestamp":" 947214907435"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214908589","data":{"timestamp":" 947214908589"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOJARIBU"," userResponse":" YALE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214910489","data":{"timestamp":" 947214910489"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOJARIBU"," userResponse":" ILIYOFUATA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214912703","data":{"timestamp":" 947214912703"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOJARIBU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214918186","data":{"timestamp":" 947214918186"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHUMA"," userResponse":" KUCHUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214918190","data":{"timestamp":" 947214918190"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNDA"," userResponse":" TUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214919191","data":{"timestamp":" 947214919191"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214922006","data":{"timestamp":" 947214922006"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" PEKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214923572","data":{"timestamp":" 947214923572"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214923935","data":{"timestamp":" 947214923934"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214925627","data":{"timestamp":" 947214925626"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214927318","data":{"timestamp":" 947214927318"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214929584","data":{"timestamp":" 947214929584"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WACHA"," userResponse":" MTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214932572","data":{"timestamp":" 947214932572"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WACHA"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214934002","data":{"timestamp":" 947214934001"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WACHA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214934305","data":{"timestamp":" 947214934305"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" LANGU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214935986","data":{"timestamp":" 947214935986"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" HILO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214935989","data":{"timestamp":" 947214935989"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214935992","data":{"timestamp":" 947214935992"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LANGU"," userResponse":" LANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214939832","data":{"timestamp":" 947214939832"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214943058","data":{"timestamp":" 947214943058"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NILILIONA"," userResponse":" TUNDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214945349","data":{"timestamp":" 947214945349"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NILILIONA"," userResponse":" TUNDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214947210","data":{"timestamp":" 947214947209"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILILIONA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214947990","data":{"timestamp":" 947214947990"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214951108","data":{"timestamp":" 947214951108"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214952087","data":{"timestamp":" 947214952087"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi nililiona kwanza!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214955397","data":{"timestamp":" 947214955397"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu alichukuwa kila tunda na kuliweka ndani ya mfuko wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HALAFU"," userResponse":" START_MBAWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214958506","data":{"timestamp":" 947214958506"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu alichukuwa kila tunda na kuliweka ndani ya mfuko wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HALAFU"," userResponse":" START_NDANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214960124","data":{"timestamp":" 947214960124"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu alichukuwa kila tunda na kuliweka ndani ya mfuko wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HALAFU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214961714","data":{"timestamp":" 947214961714"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu alichukuwa kila tunda na kuliweka ndani ya mfuko wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHUKUWA"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214962793","data":{"timestamp":" 947214962793"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu alichukuwa kila tunda na kuliweka ndani ya mfuko wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHUKUWA"," userResponse":" START_MBAWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214964764","data":{"timestamp":" 947214964763"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu alichukuwa kila tunda na kuliweka ndani ya mfuko wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHUKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214967370","data":{"timestamp":" 947214967370"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu alichukuwa kila tunda na kuliweka ndani ya mfuko wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214972321","data":{"timestamp":" 947214972321"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu alichukuwa kila tunda na kuliweka ndani ya mfuko wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TUNDA"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214973645","data":{"timestamp":" 947214973645"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu alichukuwa kila tunda na kuliweka ndani ya mfuko wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" TUNDA"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214975248","data":{"timestamp":" 947214975247"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu alichukuwa kila tunda na kuliweka ndani ya mfuko wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNDA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214975545","data":{"timestamp":" 947214975545"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu alichukuwa kila tunda na kuliweka ndani ya mfuko wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214981860","data":{"timestamp":" 947214981860"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000107_055735"," gameId":" 215e1542-6e56-4266-a8ac-83b34be8d58f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu alichukuwa kila tunda na kuliweka ndani ya mfuko wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}